A daring love story that breaks all the rules.
Bliss is a drama, romance film directed by Lance Young.
On his wedding day, Joseph nervously admits that his
wife is not quite like other women.
But his beautiful bride is more than just the "impulsive,
compulsive, obsessive" woman he thinks he knows.
And when Joseph discovers she is hiding troubling secrets, it sends them both on a
sexual odyssey that will either destroy or redeem their relationship.
Joseph, played by Craig Sheffer.
Maria, played by Sheryl Lee.
Baltazar, played by Terence Stamp.
Tanner, played by Casey Siemaszko.
Alfred, played by Spalding Gray.
Eva, played by Lois Chiles.
Bliss is a 1997 American erotic drama film written and
directed by Lance Young, in his film debut.
It stars Sheryl Lee, Craig Sheffer, and Terence Stamp.
The film also features appearances by Lance Young's sister,
Leigh Taylor-Young, as well as Molly Parker.
The story revolves around a young married couple who are
trying to address issues impacting their sex life.
The film is also a surreptitious analysis on the teachings of tantric sex.
Media attention on the film was limited yet the
reception was divided among the critics.
It was screened during the opening of the San
Francisco International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of depression, dancing,
child abuse, bondage, abusive father.
The tone is emotional.